Wallen, Saul Papers 5012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- B.F. Goodrich Co., (Oaks, Penn.), 11/16/61 - 5/12/66 (Box 112)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision J-81), 1962 (Box 112, Folder 40)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-12), 1962 (Box 112, Folder 41)
    May 31, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-13), 1962 (Box 112, Folder 42)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-13), 1962 (Box 112, Folder 43)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision J-92), 1962 (Box 112, Folder 44)
    December 3, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-32), 1962 (Box 112, Folder 45)
    December 7, 1962
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-45), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 46)
    January 26, 1963
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision J-97), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 47)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-44), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 48)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-42), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 49)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-46), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 50)
    February 10, 1963
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-47), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 51)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-53), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 52)
    March 7, 1963
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-57), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 53)
    April 22, 1963
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-62), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 54)
    April 26, 1963
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-63), 1963 (Box 112, Folder 55)
    April 27, 1963
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-70), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 56)
    January 4, 1964
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-71), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 57)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-72), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 58)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-77), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 59)
    January 7, 1964
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-78), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 60)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-79), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 61)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-86), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 62)
    March 24, 1964
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-87), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 63)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-88), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 64)
    March 25, 1964
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-7), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 65)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-6), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 66)
    April 2, 1964
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision K-89), 1964 (Box 112, Folder 67)
    April 6, 1964
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-29), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 68)
    January 25, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-30), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 69)
    January 28, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-31), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 70)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-32), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 71)
    January 29, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-33), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 72)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-34), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 73)
    February 17, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-58), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 74)
    November 29, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-63), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 75)
    November 30, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-59), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 76)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-60), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 77)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-57), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 78)
    December 1, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-61), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 79)
    December 2, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-62), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 80)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-65), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 81)
    December 3, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-64), 1965 (Box 112, Folder 82)
    December 6, 1965
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-71), 1966 (Box 112, Folder 83)
    May 10, 1966
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-72), 1966 (Box 112, Folder 84)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-73), 1966 (Box 112, Folder 85)
    May 12, 1966
- B.F. Goodrich Co., (Oaks), 5/10/66 - B.F. Goodrich Co., (Tuscaloosa), 6/8/62 (Box 113)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-74), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision L-75), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-12), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    July 1, 1966
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-13), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-14), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-15), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    July 8, 1966
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-16), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-17), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-18), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-19), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    July 25, 1966
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-20), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-44), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-47), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    October 27, 1966
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-48), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    November 4, 1966
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-60), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    February 24, 1967
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-62), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    April 17, 1967
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-63), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-64), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-65), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    April 18, 1967
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-66), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 20)
    April 19, 1967
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-67), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 21)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-68), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 22)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Oaks, Pennsylvania) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision M-69), 1967 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-139), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 24)
    June 1, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 281 (Decision G-35), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 25)
    July 14, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5, 1953 (Box 113, Folder 26)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 5, 1953 (Box 113, Folder 27)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434, 1953 (Box 113, Folder 28)
    August 14, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-75), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 29)
    November 19, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-119), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 30)
    December 28, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-73), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 31)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Correspondence), 1955 (Box 113, Folder 32)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-74), 1955 (Box 113, Folder 33)
    March 14, 1955
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-203), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 34)
    September 22, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-204), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 35)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-205), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 36)
    October 28, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-206), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 37)
    June 18, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-208), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 38)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-209), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 39)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (American Anode, Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Withdrawn), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 40)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision G-222), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 41)
    December 13, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision J-7), 1960 (Box 113, Folder 42)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434, 1964 (Box 113, Folder 43)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision M-36), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 44)
    September 26, 1966
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Riverside, New Jersey) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 434 (Decision M-45), 1966 (Box 113, Folder 45)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-141), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 46)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-142), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 47)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-143), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 48)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-158), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 49)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-160), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 50)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-173), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 51)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-168), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 52)
    October 30, 1952
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-169), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 53)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-170), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 54)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-171), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 55)
    August 11, 1952
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-174), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 56)
    October 7, 1952
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-201), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 57)
    November 20, 1952
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-202), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 58)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-203), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 59)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-204), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 60)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-205), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 61)
    February 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision F-213), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 62)
    April 7, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-14), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 63)
    June 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-15), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 64)
    December 1952
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-16), 1952 (Box 113, Folder 65)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-18), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 66)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-53), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 67)
    September 20, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-54), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 68)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-55), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 69)
    September 21, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-86), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 70)
    December 1, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-87), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 71)
    November 30, 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-89), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 72)
    October 1953
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-91), 1953 (Box 113, Folder 73)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-153), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 74)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-154), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 75)
    April 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-180), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 76)
    August 18, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-181), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 77)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-182), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 78)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-183), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 79)
    August 20, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-184), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 80)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-185), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 81)
    August 19, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-186), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 82)
    August 21, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-187), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 83)
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Tuscaloosa, Alabama) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 351 (Decision G-188), 1954 (Box 113, Folder 84)
    August 22, 1954
  - The B.F. Goodrich Company (Watertown, Massachusetts) and United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum, and Plastic Workers of America Local 21914, 1961 (Box 113, Folder 85)
    January 14, 1961